1 Morning on the Kanko (River Han)
2 City of Keijo (Seoul)
3 South Gate Street in Keijo
4 (1) Government General Offices (2) New Building for Government General of Chosen
5 Central Council in Conference
6 KeikaiRo
7 (1) Daigari Reservoir <Reservori> (2) Fuji Fam
8 Rice for Export at Kunsan
9 (1) Model Farm (2) Fuel and Ore Dressing Institute
10 (1) Shipping of Raw Cotton (2) Bamboo Plantation
11 BotanDai
12 (1) Herring Fishing (2) Japanese Fishing Village at Toei
13 Jinsen Town Hall and Keijo Chamber of Commerce
14 Public Cocoon Agency
15 (1) Suigen Cattle Market (2) Taikyu Market
16 (1) Heijo Sugar Manufactory (2) Factory of Chosen Reeling Company
17 Mitsubishi Ironworks
18 (1) Port of Jinsen (2) Port of Seishin
19 (1) Government Afforestation (2) Radampo Waterfall
20 (1) HyakushoRo (2) ReinanRo
21 Korean Ginseng Field
22 (1) Saltpans at Koryo Bay (2) Tobacco Planting at Chushu
23 (1) Kanjo Ginko (2) Keijo Branch of Oriental Development Company
24 Chosen Shrine
25 Preparatory School of Keijo Imperial University
26 (1) Suigen Higher Agricultural & Dendrological School (2) Riri Agricultural & Forestry School
27 (1) Taiden Middle School (2) Keijo Second Public Girls' High School
28 (1) Kaishu Higher Common School (2) Keijo Girls' Higher Common School
29 Provincial Normal School at Keijo
30 Seishu Primary School and Shingishu Common School
31 (1) Government General Library (2) Railway Library
</8>

32 ShokeiEn
33 Chosen Art Exhibition
34 KeigakuIn
35 (1) KoshoEn (2) Olympic<Oliympic> Trial Meeting
36 (1) Archery Contest (2) GyujiDo
37 Kokwamon Telephone Branch Office and Jinsen Post Office
38 (1) Motor<Moter> Boats (2) Iron Bridge over Yalu
39 Chosen Hotel
40 Government General Hospital
41 (1) Visiting Doctors (2) Kunsan Provincial Hospital
42 Taikyu Waterworks Reservoir 
43 (1) Salvation Amy Children's Home (2) Severance Hospital
44 (1) Blind & Deaf Mute Department of SaiseiIn (2) KojoKan Hall
45 City of Heijo
46 Chukochin and Keizan Police Stations
47 Supreme Court
48 (1) Taikyu Appeal Court (2) Shingishu Local Court
49 Roman Catholic Church and HonganJi Branch Temple
50 (1) Shakuo Temple (2) Fuseki Temple
51 BukkokuJi and SekkutsuAn
52 Mural Painting on Old Tomb at Kosai
53 (1) Site of Hangetsujo and Heisaito
54 (1) Swinging at Kaijyo (2) Lantern Festival at Kaijyo
55 Washing and Fulling
56 (1) Hot spring of Torai (2) Hot spring of Jujyo
57 Bathing at Gensan
58 Korean Villages
59 (1) Marriage (2) Visiting Graves
60 New Bambutsuso in KongoSan (Diamond Mountain)
61 GyokuryuKei in KongoSan
62 BogunDai in Inner Kongo
63 SosekiTei
</9>

MORNING ON THE KANKO(RIVER HAN)
</10>

( 2 )

CITY OF KEIJO (SEOUL)
Keijo, formerly called Hansong or Hanyang, was the capital of Old Korea for more than five centuries and is today the seat of the Government General of Chosen, and the very heart, politically and otherwise, of the country. The economic development of recent years has brought in its train readjustment of its streets and erection of modern buildings as well as establishment of cultural institutions, and in its entirely new aspect the city bears good comparison to any premier cities in Japan. The most recent figures put the population at over 280,000, of which Japanese number 70,000, In the right background of the picture can be seen a great edifice which will become the new home of the Government as soon as its interior is finished, while the classical stone building in the left front is the Bank of Chosen.
</12>

( 3 )

NANDAIMON DORI, KEIJO
The picture gives a view of the best part of Nandaimondori or South Gate Street, one of the ancient thoroughfares of Keijo and the first of its streets to be improved. The roadway is 77 feet in width and the pavements are each 21 feet wide, while the road surface is tarmacadamized throughout its entire length.
</13>

( 4 )

GOVERNMENT GENERAL OFFICES
The wooden buildings shown below were originally erected for the former Residency General, and on the establishment of the present regime were taken over as its offices after being repaired and some additions made. They stand at the foot of the hill on the south side of Keijo.

NEW BUILDING FOR GOVERNMENT GENERAL
The new building for the Government General in the grounds of North Palace is of ferroconcrete and five stories high, including attic and basement, covering an area of 1,115 tsubo. Actual construction is already completed and the interior is now being fitted up. It was started as a ten year undertaking in 1916; the cost amounting to about 6,500,000 yen in all.
</14>

( 5 )

CENTRAL COUNCIL IN CONFERENCE
As the highest Korean consulting body for the Governor General the Central Council is organized of a President, Vice President, 5 advisers, and 65 councilors<councillors>. The building was erected during the Protectorate regime, and was later given over to the Central Council to serve as its offices.
</17>

( 6 )

KEIKAIRO PAVILION
This structure stands in the precincts of Keifuku or North Palace. It was rebuilt on the foundation laid in the early years of the Yi Fra, and the paved portion covers an area of more than 150 tsubo. The tall pillars are of granite, 48 in number, and support a pavilion in which public entertainments were given in former times. There is a lotus pond around the building with a miniature island in it, and the whole presents a most fascinating view by reason of the harmonious blending of natural and artificial beauty.
</18>

-7

FUJI FARM
Fuji Farms under the management of the Fuji Industrial Company are found in various parts of the peninsula, the chief among them being the one lying east of Kunsan with an area of 1,850 chobu newly formed out of dry beach. Both Japanese and Korean settlers are invited to the land thus brought under cultivation.
DAIGARI RESERVOIR
This modern reservoir, constructed by the Yeliyoku Irrigation Association, is situated in Daigari, North Zenra Province. It was formed by building a dam across a canyon with a content of 10,000 cubic tsubo and 100 feet in height. When the reservoir is fill, it has a surface area of 143 chobu, the volume of water amounting to 720,000,000 cubic feet, sufficient to irrigate an area of 10,000 chobu.
</19>

( 8 )

SHIPPING RICE AT KUNSAN
The export of Korean rice to Japan is increasing in volume year by year, as is the yield, and of recent years reaches nearly 5,000,000 koku, of which about one-third is shipped at Kunsan.
</20>

( 9 )

MODEL FARM
The model Farm at Suigen near Keijo is the central organ for the promotion of agriculture under the direct control of the Government General, with branches for horticulture, cotton planting, or stock faming, in Tokuson and other places. It was established by the Residency General in 1906 and has contributed much toward the agricultural development of the peninsula.

FUEL AND OREDHESSING LABORATORY
This institution, situated in an outskirt of Keijo on the bank of the River Han, is attached to the Industrial Bureau, and was founded in 1922 for the purpose of studying the motive power capacity of various fuels and of promoting thereby the mining industry of Chosen.
</21>

( 10 )

BAMBOO PLANTATION
The bamboo forests in the district of kato, South Keisho Province, are under the management of the Oriental Development<Eevelopment> Company and cover an area of about 90 chobu in all.

SHIPPING OF RAW COTTCON
The area under cotton in Chosen is 158,000 chobu and its yearly crop is estimated at 130,0000,000 kin. The cultivation of American cotton is encouraged in the south, while that of native species is grown in the north. The chief provinces producing American cotton are South Zenra and North and South Keisho, and their production reaches some 100,000,000 kin, the bulk of which is shipped at Mokpo to Japan.
</22>

( 13 )

JINSEN TOWN HALL AND KEIJO CHAMBER OF COMMERCE
A Chamber of Commerce in Chosen is conducted in much the same manner as in Japan, the only difference being that it has a joint membership of Japanese and Koreans. Keijo Chamber of commerce is one of line in Chosen. Its upper story<storey> is used as a public hall. Both it and Jinsen Town Hall have been built but recently.
</26>

( 14 )

PUBLIC COCOON AGENCY
The climate of Chosen is well adapted to sericulture, which has shown remarkable progress lately as a result of the encouragement given to it, and the production of cocoons in 1923 amounted to 207,000 koku. Cocoons are produced in every province, North Keisho, South Zenra, South Chusei, and North Heian being the foremost. The picture shows the sale of cocoons at the public agency at Anto, North Keisho Province.
</27>

( 15 )

SUIGEN CATTLE MARKET AND TAIKYU MARKET
Markets are still important business organs in Korean country towns, and are regularly held every fifth or sixth day. They number more than 1,200 in all, and their annual transactions reach up to 120,000,000 yen. The largest of them are Taikyu Market and Suigen Market, though the latter deals only in cattle. The yearly business done by both amounts respectively to some 2,700,000 and 600,000 yen.
</30>

( 16 )

HEIJO SUGAR MANUFACTORY
Heijo Sugar Manufactory is a branch of the Japan Sugar Company and was established in 1920 as the pioneer plant of its kind in the peninsula. It turns out sugar from beet and refines raw sugar imported from abroad. Experiments<Expriments> carried on for a number of years prove that Heijo and district are well suited for the cultivation of the sugar beet.

FACTORY OF CHOSEN REELING COMPANY
This Company is under the sole management of Koreans and engages in the production and sale of silk thread and cocoons. It was formed in 1919 with a capital of 1,000,000 yen. Its offices and works are in one of the outskirts of Keijo.
</31>

( 19 )

GOVERNMENT AFFORESTATION
This picture gives a view in their 17th year of the trees planted by the Government in 1907 for the prevention of sand slides. The forest is on Niwo Hill in the western part of Keijo.

RADAMPO WATERBALL
This waterfall is in the upper part of the Yalu, about 10 miles east of Shinkabachin. Large rocks in the river bed cause rapids here, making the passage most difficult. The trees felled on both sides, Korean and Manchurian, of the Upper Yalu are made into rafts and floated down the river through many such rapids to Shingishu or Antoken.
</35>

( 20 )

HYAKUSHORO
This pavilion stands on a hill in the northern part of Anshu, South Heian Province. It was built about 500 years ago and is now preserved as a national treasure, as it is resplendent with antique elegance. The site commands a superb view of the River Seisen and the valley of Anshu.

PEINANRO
This pavilion is situated at the eastern end of the town of Mitsuyo in South Keisho Province. It has a fine view of a vast spreading field with the River Gisen gleaming just in front of it and the peaks of Ryuto and Shuan standing on either side. The building, the only part remaining of the ancient Reinan Temple, is now under national care.
</36>

( 21 )

KOREAN GINSENG FIELD
"Ginseng is a perennial herb belonging to the Araliaceae family. Medical ginseng is prepared from the root of a plant usually carefully tended for 6 years, the first year being passed in a seedling bed. Red ginseng, widely known as Koryu ginseng, is made from a select"" variety by a special method in Kaijo under the direction of the Government Monopoly Bureau. All other varieties are freely made into so-called white ginseng by the people by drying the root in the sun."""
</39>

( 22 )

SALTPANS AT KORYO BAY
The native method of making salt is by boiling. The first experiment in obtaining salt by natural evaporation was made by the Government during the years 1909-1912 by laying out some 1,000 chobu of land for the purpose at Shuan near Jinsen and at Koryo Bay near Chinnampo. Of late years the area has been enlarged and now covers about 2,000 chobu.

TOBACCO PLANTING AT CHUSHU
Chushu in North Chusei Province is the chief producer of tobacco, and of late has become noted for its production of yellow tobacco. A subbranch of the Monopoly Bureau is situated here.
</40>

( 23 )

KANJO GINKO
This was established in 1903, and most of its shareholders are Koreans. The capital of the Bank is 6,000,000 yen, and its head office is in Keijo with branches in Tokyo and Osaka, and in every important centre in the peninsula.

KEIJO BRANCH OF ORIENTAL DEVELOPMENT COMPANY
This Company is a special establishment engaged in opening up and developing the peninsula assisted by the Government. It is capitalized at 50,000,000 yen and has its head office in Tokyo with branches in various places in Chosen and Manchuria.
</43>

( 24 )

CHOSEN SHRINE
Chosen Shrine is a grand State shrine dedicated to Amaterasu Omikami, the Japanese sungoddess, and to the Great Emperor Meiji, as a centre for national ceremonies. It is situated on South Hill in Keijo, and its completion is expected in the fiscal year 1925, the cost of it being estimated at 1,500,000 yen. The sacred ground covers 7,000 tsubo in area, and the inner and outer garden cover a total of 200, 000 tsubo.
</44>

( 25 )

PREPARATORY SCHOOL OF KEIJO IMPERIAL UNIVERSITY
The Korean educational system, from elementary school to college, is nearly the same as that in Japan, and it is now arranged that the Imperial University founded in Keijo under the University Ordinance shall be opened in 1926. As preliminary work a preparatory school was started in the above building in May, 1924.
</47>

( 26 )

HIGHER AGRICULTURAL DENDROLOGICAL SCHOOL AT SUIGEN
This was originally founded as an attached institution to the Model Farm in 1906, and in 1918 was brought under the immediate supervision of the Government. In April, 1922, it was raised to the status of a college, and its courses of instruction greatly improved.

AGRICULTURAL AND FORESTRY SCHOOL AT RIRI
This secondary school was opened in April, 1922, under the direct control of the Government. The picture represents the planting of rice by students of the school.
</48>

( 27 )

MIDDLE SCHOOL AT TAIDEN
Middle Schools in Chosen are of exactly the same standard as those in Japan, and though they are primarily for Japanese boys, Koreans are admitted under certain circumstances.

SECOND GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL AT KEIJO
Girls' High Schools in Chosen are also of the same standard as those in Japan, and though they are chiefly for Japanese girls, attendance by Korean girls is allowed under certain conditions.
</51>

( 28 )

HIGHER COMMON SCHOOL AT KAISHU
A Higher Common School corresponds to a Middle School and chiefly receives Korean boys. While the educational system in Chosen is similar to that in Japan, the difference in language and customs of the two peoples has necessitated division of public schools into two kinds, one for Japanese and the other for Koreans. However, the course of study, qualification of graduates<garduates>, and connection<connexion> with higher schools are quite the same in both cases. Public schools, other than those for common education, receive both races on equal footing.

GIRLS'HIGHER COMMON SCHOOL AT KEIJO
This also corresponds to a Girls' High School. It is chiefly for Korean girls.
</52>

( 29 )

PROVINCIAL<PROVINCIL> NORMAL SCHOOL AT KEIJO
Normal schools in Chosen are of two kinds, Central and Provincial. There is one central institution, Keijo Normal School, with a six year course, 5 years in the general and 1 year in the practical course. As for other normal schools, there is one in each province, their course being three or two years.
</55>

( 30 )

PRIMARY SCHOOL AT SEISHU AND COMMON SCHOOL AT SHINGISHU
A Primary School for Japanese children in Chosen is just the same as that in the homeland. A Common School for Korean children has a course of 4 to 6 years, those with a six year course ranking in the same grade as Japanese Primary Schools. In special circumstances it is allowable for Koreans to enter public schools for Japanese and vice versa.
</56>

( 31 )

GOVERNMENT GENERAL LIBRARY
This new library, which is under the direct management of the Government, is in South Gate Street. It was built in the spring of 1924.

RAILWAY LIBRARY
This library is situated at Ryusan, Keijo. It was founded by the South Manchuria Railway Company and taken over by the Railway Bureau of the Government General on the retransfer to it of the Railways in Chosen.
</59>

( 32 )

SHOKEIEN
Shokeien is that part of the grounds of Shotoku or East Palace thrown open to the general public. It contains a museum and zoological and botanical gardens. The building on the terrace is the Art Gallery, in which excellent specimens of Korean fine arts dating from olden times are on view.
</60>

-35

KOSHOEN
Koshoen is a quiet spot surrounded by thick pine woods on a hill at Kyuryusan outside the city proper of Keijo. The golf course opened here a few years ago enjoys a pleasant location, presenting to golfers a different view of every green. But this ground is now transferred to Seiryori, another suburb of Keijo, where a new course has but lately been provided.

OLYMPIC TRIAL MEETING
This is a view of the all Chosen Olympic trial meeting held at Kunrenin Ground in Keijo in May, 1924.
</64>

-36

ARCHERY CONTEST
In old Korea archery was regarded as one of the most important military arts, and was included among the subjects of examination of military officers. Thus the Korean military class put great stress upon archery, making training grounds for it in local centres and holding contests regularly every year. It is still pursued as a popular sport.

GYUJIDO
In a suburb of Keijo, at the foot of Mount Hokkan, is a small valley called Gyujido noted for its cherryblossoms. The trees are century old and are of Japanese origin. In the spring they make a real flowery canopy and invite thousands of pleasure seekers. It can be reached by automobile from Keijo or by rail to Sodo on the KeiGen Line and thence by a walk of two miles.
</65>

-37

KOKANON TELEPHONE BRANCH OFFICE
This office was established in December, 1922, when the city of Keijo was divided, so far as the telephone service is concerned, into three districts, viz., Central, Ryuzan, and Kokamon.

JINSEN POST OFFICE
This is one of the oldest post offices in Chosen, having been established by the Japanese Government as early as 1880. The building shown below was completed in November<Novermber>, 1923.
</68>

-38

MOTOR BOATS
Motor boats being of light draught and fast are well suited for navigating rivers. In Chosen there are 4 in use on the Yalu and 2 on the Kan for the carrying of passengers, and their routes measure respectively over 300 miles and 150 miles. There is also a smaller one plying on the Rakutoko.

IRON BRIDGE OVER YALU
The iron bridge spanning the Yalu connects the Manchurian Railway with the Korean trunk line, and was built by the Railway Bureau of the Government General in 1911. It is 3,090 feet long, with a footway 8 foot wide on either side. The centre span of the bridge opens to allow the passage of ships on the river.
</69>

-39

CHOSEN HOTEL
The Chosen hotel was opened to business in 1914 by the Railway Department of the Government General. The building in foreign style cost 840,000 yen to erect. It has over 80 rooms with a spacious dining room, big hall, and lovely garden, and is counted among the foremost in the Orient, its up-to-date accommodation being well known to tourists.
</72>

-40

GOVERNMENT GENERAL HOSPITAL
This central medical organ of Chosen was in existence in preannexation days, and has since been greatly enlarged. Recently<Recentry> extension work has been undertaken in both building and equipment at great cost to secure a thoroughly up-to-date institution in every respect.
</73>

-41

VISITING DOCTORS
In Chosen the distribution of medical organs is still far from adequate. This, coupled with the slight sanitary knowledge of the people, has necessitated the founding of Provincial Hospitals in the principal centres and the appointment of public doctors to remoter parts. But to those parts of the country still beyond the reach of these medical provisions, doctors from the nearest Hospital are sent periodically. The picture represents doctors on such a visit.

PROVINCIAL HOSPITAL AT KUNSAN
A Provincial Hospital is maintained with the interest from the Imperial donation fund specially granted to Chosen and an annual subsidy from the Government General. These hospitals, now 26 in number, are found in each provincial capital and other towns. The picture represents one of the more recent establishments<establishements>. 
</76>

-42

WATERWORKS RESERVOIR AT TAIKYU
Most of the waterworks in Chosen were established by the Government, and later on transferred to public bodies, such as municipalities and townships. At present Keijo and 24 other towns are provided with waterworks. The reservoir at Taikyu under municipal management is large enough to supply 30,000 people.
</77>

-43

SALVATION ARMY CHILDREN'S HOME
This is maintained by the Korean headquarters of the Salvation Army in Keijo, and its object is to receive helpless or homeless children and give them suitable training. This Home was started a few years ago with the aid of voluntary contributions from many quarters.

SEVERANCE HOSPITAL
This hospital, situated outside the South Gate, Keijo, is maintained by American Mission Boards and has a medical college attached to it. The hospital has been in existence for many years and is of great medical service to the country.
</80>

-44

BLIND AND DEAF-MUTE DEPARTMENT OF SAISETIN ASYLUM
The Saiseiin in Keijo is a charitable organization established with 500,000 yen of the Imperial donation fund specially granted to Chosen. At present it is divided into two parts, orphanage and blind and deaf-mute department. The picture shows the deaf mutes practicing<practising> sewing.

KOJOKAN HALL
The Kojokan Hall is under the management of a Japanese Buddhist Mission at Tennendo, Keijo. It aims at the social enlightenment<enlightement> of Koreans, and has three departments, cultural, educational, and industrial.
</81>

-45

CITY OF HEIJO
Heijo is the city in which Chitzu founded his kingdom, to be supplanted long afterwards by the kingdom of Kokuryu which lasted for about 700 years. It stands on the bank of the River Daido and occupies a most prominent position in the west, and especially so in an economic sense. The population of late has passed the 100,000 mark, and in prosperity the city ranks next to Keijo. It promises to become a great industrial centre in no distant future.
</84>

-46

CHUKOCHIN AND KEIZAN POLICE STATIONS
The Korean frontier, bounded by the rivers Yalu and Tumen, extends hundreds of miles, and in the more inaccessible parts of it both traffic and defence are very difficult. Thus the 2,500 police stationed at posts at intervals of about 5 miles from each other are quite deserving of sympathy. The picture represents two of the more important of those outlying stations, the one in Chukochin, North Heian, and the other in Keizan, South Kankyo.
</85>

-47

SUPREME COURT
The Supreme Court in Chosen is substantially equivalent to the one in Japan. The building situated in Teido, Keijo, was erected during the Protectorate regime as offices for the Board of Finance of the Korean Government.
</88>

-48

COURT OF APPEAL AT TAIKYU
The Court of Appeal in Chosen is a court of the second instance, and combines the duties discharged by a local court of review and an appellate court in Japan. There are three in Chosen, viz., in Keijo, Heijo, and Taikyu, which last was built in 1923.

SCENE IN LOCAL COURT AT SHINGISHU
A Local Court in Chosen is simply a court of the first instance, and there are 12 of them in all, though some part of their business is done by branch offices established in 52 important places. Examination and trial are conducted exactly as in Japan.
</89>

-49

ROMAN GATHOLIC CHURCH AND HONGANJI
The Roman Catholic Church under the control of the French Catholic Evangelical<Evengelical> Mission stands on a height in Meijimachi, Keijo. This Mission was the pioneer in spreading the gospel of Christianity in the peninsula.

Honganji, a Buddhist Temple situated at the foot of South Hill in Keijo, is the propagating headquarters of the Otani Sect of Japanese Buddhism in Chosen. This sect was the first to send men into the peninsula.
</92>

-50

SHAKUOJI
This ancient temple, one of the greatest in Chosen, was erected by the Founder of the Yi Dynasty, and was rebuilt in the middle of the same era. There is an array of classic buildings still unchanged, bespeaking the splendour of those days, while the natural objects around add preeminently to the beauty of the place. The temple is about 3 miles northeast of Shakuoji Station.

FUSEKIJI
This temple stands on Mount Taihaku in North Keisho Province. The Muryoden, its main building, is the oldest and finest structure in Chosen, and is as precious a monument to the country as is Horyu Temple to Japan. The building, 700 years old, with its images of Buddha and its carvings, which are all masterpieces comparable in effect to the art productions of the Nara Period in Japan, is now the only specimen remaining of the architecture in the most palmy days of the Koryu Era.
</93>

-51

BUKKOKUJI AND SEKKUTSUAN
Bukkokuji is an old Buddhist temple situated on the western slope of Mount Togan, 10 miles from Keishu, the old capital of Silla. Vairocana in the Daiyuden Hall and Amitabha in the Gokurakuden Hall, both bronze statues, are typical of the art of illa, as are Tahoto and Shakato, two pagodas, near by.

Sekkutsuan is a holy cave on the same mountain and about 2 miles from Bukkokuji. It is lined with granite and in the centre of it stands a large stone statue of Buddha, while on the walls themselves are carved images of two Giants, four Deva Kings, an eleven faced Goddess of mercy, great Disciples, and a number of Celestial Saints. All are representative works of the period.
</96>

-52

MURAL PAINTING ON OLD TOMB AT KOSAI
Some of the rarest relics of old Korea are the tombs at Kosai, South Heian Province. There are three great sepulchres, about 1,350 years old, and the vaults and stone coffins are of exquisite workmanship.

Especially beautiful are the paintings on the walls. These are all expressive of the style of art prevailing during a certain period in ancient China and Japan, and are cherished as among the oldest examples of Oriental art. The picture shows a mural painting of the Dragon, one of the four sacred animals.
</97>

-54

SWINGING AT KAIJO
According to native custom the 5th of May of the lunar calendar is the one and only holiday for Korean girls throughout the year. On this day they dress in their best and gather in a field to enjoy themselves, mostly by swinging under a big tree.

LANTERN FESTIVAL AT KALJO
Kaijo was formerly a great stronghold of Buddhism, and the 8th of April of the lunar calendar, that is the birthday of Buddha, is still celebrated there in a most enthusiastic way. In the evening every street is decorated with lanterns of various kinds and lighted at dusk, making the entire town a sea of light, attracting crowds of visitors to it from far and near.
</100>

-55

WASHING AND FULLING
Korean women of the lower class have the custom of washing their clothes in nearby streams in groups. The rhythmic<rythmic> sound of their paddling fills the air and gives a peculiarly Korean touch to the surroundings. The above picture represents a scene at a public washing place. The fulling block is of stone, which explains why the sound of fulling is mellow and charming
</101>

-56

HOT SPRING OF TORAI
This Spa, one of the most noted in Chosen, is five miles northeast of Busan<Fusan>, and can be reached by tramcar or automobile. In the vicinity are Bongyoji, a temple, and other places well worth a visit.

HOT SPRING OF JUJYO
This Spa is the latest discovery and lies seven miles northwest of Taiden Station, from which it may be reached by automobile. The place being quite new it does not yet attract many visitors, but promises to become popular in a few years to come. It is a quiet resort full of rural beauty.
</104>

-57

BATHING AT GENSAN
This gives a view of Shoteiri at the eastern end of Gensan, which is a beautiful beach with a wide stretch of white sand and green pines skirting it. The water here is very clear. In the season suitable accommodation is provided, and there is always a great rush of people to this summer resort.
</105>

-58

KOREAN VILLAGES
Korean villages are generally found in places easy of access to fuel and water, with sunny hills behind and open fields in front. The structure of their houses is most simple, yet with an eye to making them weather proof and for warming arrangements their lower part is built of stone and clay, while the roof is low and thatched thick with straw. Some of the villages are occupied by families having but one surname among them. The picture represents the purely Korean quarter in Kaijo. The water from the spring in the stream is used for drinking, and the stones around for wash boards.
</108>

-59

MARRIAGE
By age long custom, a marriage, whatever may by class the parties belong to, is always conducted at the bride's home after which the bridegroom takes her to his own house, and there the ceremony is concluded. The picture shows a newly wedded couple of the middle class on their way to the bridegroom's<briedgroom's> house, a bridal procession so to speak, he in a rikisha and she in a palanquin.

VISITING GRAVES
Koreans have a pious regard for their ancestors and make it a rule to visit their graves or a certain day in both spring and autumn, and after making them clean and tidy place before them wine, fruit, and dried meat in toked of homage. When the ancestral tombs are too far distant a grave keeper is employed to perform this service.
</109>

-60

NEW BANBUTSUSO IN KONGOSAN (DIAMOND MOUNTAIN)
Banbutsuso is situated some 5 miles northwest Onseri, a small town in the mountain, and of forming part of Kanka Valley is classed with Kyuryuen of Gyokuryu Valley as the grandest view of Outer Kongo, though it really goes under four names, Old, New, Inner, and Rear Banbutsuso. It consists of a great cluster of gigantic and fantastic rocks towering high in the air and presents indeed a wonderful sight, at once unique and incomparable in the world.
</111>

-61

GYOKURYUKEL IN KONGOSAN
This valley is the most picturesque part of all Outer Kongo and is traversed by a stream coming from Biroho, the highest of a thousand peaks in the mountain. The water, limpid as crystal, flows down a deep ravine amid strangely shaped stones and rocks, here dashing into rapids, and there falling into pools, and thus makes the place a veritable fairy land. Along the stream are to be seen many lovely sights, each known by its own name.
</112>

-62

BOGUN DAL IN INNER KONGO
Bogundai is situated<situaed> about 2 miles northwest of Choanji, a starting point for the ascent of Inner Kongo. It is one of the highest of the mountain peaks, so the view obtained from its summit is simply superb, taking in the magnificent panorama spread out below and all around. Tradition says that when Silla was once in critical danger from an attack by Koryn, Prince Ema escaped to the mountain with his followers, and from the top of this peak watched the movement of the enemy and was thus able to gain the victory. Hence it has been called Bogundai or Troop watching Height.
</115>

-63

SOSEKITEI
Sosekitei is the name given to a rocky promontory situated east of Kotei on the east coast of the peninsula. It is composed of a cluster of basaltic columns of huge dimensions, many of them, seventy feet high, rising sheer from the sparkling water, and is in very truth one of the most marvellous works of nature.
</116>
